Jascha Heifetz Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1911-1974 (Box 1-247)
  - Music by Other Composers (Box-folder 15/2-11, Box 16-247)
    - Composers
      - Enesco, Georges
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op. 6], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 78/6)
      - Ernst, Heinrich Wilhelm
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 23, F-sharp minor], Parts (Box-folder 78/7-8, Box-folder 79/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 23, F-sharp minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 79/2)
        - [Fantasie brillante sur la marche et la romance de G. Rossini, violin, orchestra], Orchestral parts (Box-folder 79/3)
        - [Fantasie brillante sur la marche et la romance de G. Rossini, violin, orchestra; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 79/4)
        - [Ungarische Melodien, violin, orchestra, op. 22], Parts (Box-folder 79/5, Box-folder 80/1)
        - [Ungarische Melodien, op. 22, violin, orchestra; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 80/2)
      - Fairchild, Blair
        - Danse russe, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 80/3)
        - Scherzando, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 80/4)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 27], Score (Box-folder 80/5)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 27], Parts (Box-folder 80/5)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 24], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 80/6)
      - Falla, Manuel de
        - Danse de la frayeur, Piano score (Box-folder 80/7)
        - Pantomime, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 80/8)
        - Seven spanish folk-songs, Piano-vocal score and part (Box-folder 80/9)
        - Suite populaire Espagnole, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 80/10)
        - Suite populaire Espagnole: Jota, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 80/11)
        - Danse du meunier, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Joseph Szigeti (Box-folder 80/12)
        - Fandango, Piano score (Box-folder 81/1)
        - Danse espagnole, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 81/2)
      - Fauré, Gabriel
        - Après un rêve, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 81/3)
        - [Berceuse, op. 16], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 81/4)
        - [La bonne chanson, op. 61], Piano-violin score (Box-folder 81/5)
        - [Pavane, op. 50], Full score (Box-folder 81/6)
        - Fileuse, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 81/7)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 15, C minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 81/8)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, no. 2, op. 45, G minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 81/9)
        - Nocturne, Piano-cello/violin score and part (Box-folder 81/10)
        - [Sicilienne, op. 78], Piano-cello score and part (Box-folder 81/11)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op. 13, A major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 81/12)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 120, D minor], Piano score and part (Box-folder 82/1)
        - Album of twenty songs, Piano-vocal score; 3 vols. (Box-folder 82/2)
      - Ferguson, Howard
        - [Sonata, violin, no. 1, op. 2], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 82/3)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 2, op. 10], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 82/4)
      - Flesch, Carl
        - Problems of tone production in violin playing, Musical examples and text (Box-folder 82/5)
        - Urstudien for violin, Musical examples and text (Box-folder 82/6)
      - Finney, Ross Lee
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 4, A minor], Score (Box-folder 82/7)
      - Fiocco, Joseph-Hector
        - [Allegro; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 82/8)
      - Foch, Dirk
        - [Prelude, op. 17, no. 2], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 82/9)
      - Foss, Lukas
        - Composer's holiday, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 82/10)
        - Dedication, Photostat and negative photostat of piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 83/1)
        - Early song, Photostat of piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 83/2)
        - Early song, Negative photostat of piano-violin score part (Box-folder 83/2)
        - [Quartet, strings, G major], Miniature score (Box 210)
      - Foster, Stephen
        - [The old oaken bucket; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 83/3)
      - Françaix, Jean
        - [Suite, violin and orchestra; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 83/4)
        - [Trio, strings], Parts (Box-folder 83/5)
      - Franck, César
        - [Quartet, strings, D major], Parts (Box-folder 83/6)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, F minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 83/7)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, A major], Piano-violin score and parts (Box-folder 83/8)
        - [Symphony, D minor], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 1, no. 1], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 83/9)
      - Friedman, Erick See: Paganini, Nicoló for cadenza to violin concerto (folder 135/10)
      - Friedman, Ignacy
        - [Les révérences; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 83/10)
      - Gardner, Samuel
        - From the canebrake, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 84/1)
        - [From the canebrake; arr.], Photostat of holograph string quartet score (Box-folder 84/2)
      - Gaubert, Philippe
        - Quatre esquisses, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 84/3)
      - Gershwin, George
        - Embraceable you, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 84/4)
        - The man I love, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 84/5)
      - Gingold, Josef
        - Orchestral excerpts from the symphonic repertoire for violin, Violin score; Folders: 84/6 Volume 1 84/7 Volume 2 84/8 Volume 3 (Box-folder 84/6-8)
      - Glazunov, Alexander
        - [Concerto, piano, op. 92, F minor; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 85/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 82, A minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 85/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 82, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 85/3-5)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 82, A minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 86/1)
        - Jour de fête, String quartet parts (Box-folder 86/2)
        - [Méditation, op. 32], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 86/3)
        - [Novellettes, op. 15], String quartet parts (Box-folder 86/4)
        - [Novellettes, op. 15], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 1, op. 1, D major], Parts (Box-folder 86/5)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 1, op. 1, D major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 3, op. 26, G major], Parts (Box-folder 86/6)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 4, op. 64, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 86/7)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 5, op. 70, D minor], Parts (Box-folder 86/8)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 5, op. 70, D minor], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 6, op. 106, B-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 86/9)
        - [Quintet, strings, op. 39], Parts (Box-folder 87/1)
        - [Raymonda, op. 57; arr.], Piano score (Box-folder 87/2)
        - [Raymonda, op. 57. Grand adagio; arr.], Piano-violin score (Box-folder 87/3)
        - [Raymonda, op. 57. Valse; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 87/4)
        - [Stenka razine, op. 13], Orchestral score (Box-folder 87/5)
        - [Suite, op. 35], String quartet parts (Box-folder 87/6)
      - Glière, Reinhold
        - [Duets, violin, cello, op. 38], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 87/7)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 2], Parts (Box-folder 88/1)
        - [Red poppy. Dance of the Soviet sailors; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 88/2)
      - Glinka, Mikhail
        - Das Leben für den Zaren, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Das Leben für den Zaren, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 88/3)
      - Glinka, Mikhail; Milii Balakirev
        - [L'Alouette; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 88/4)
      - Gluck, Christoph Willibald von
        - [Alceste; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 88/5)
        - [Iphigenie in Aulis. Overture], Miniature (Box 211)
        - Melodie, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 89/1)
      - Godard, Benjamin
        - Canzonetta, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 89/2)
        - Canzonetta, Piano-violin score (Box-folder 89/3)
        - [Duets, violins (2), piano], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 89/4)
        - Lullaby, Piano-violin/cello score and part (Box-folder 89/5)
        - [Jocelyn. Lullaby; arr.], Ms. piano-violin-voice score (Box-folder 242/6)
        - [Jocelyn. Lullaby; arr.], Piano-violin-voice score (Box-folder 89/6)
      - Godowsky, Leopold
        - Avowal, Photostat of holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 89/7)
        - Larghetto lamentoso, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 89/8)
        - Legende, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 89/9)
        - Perpetuum mobile, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 89/10)
        - Valse, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 89/11)
        - Valse macabre, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 89/12)
        - Viennese, Piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 89/13)
        - Miniatures, Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 89/14)
        - Sylvan Tyrol, Holograph piano score (Box-folder 89/15)
        - A Watteau paysage, Holograph piano score (Box-folder 89/16)
        - Alt Wien, Holograph piano score (Box-folder 89/17)
        - Memories, Holograph piano score (Box-folder 89/18)
        - Waltz poem (no. 1), Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 90/1)
      - Goetschius, Marjorie
        - I dream of you more than you dream I do, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/2)
        - Lament, Holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 90/3)
        - The last time I saw you, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/4)
        - New moon in New Mexico, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/5)
      - Goldmark, Rubin
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 28, A minor], Orchestral score (2) (Box-folder 90/6)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 28, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 90/7-8)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 28, A minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 91/1)
        - [Ländliche Hochzeit, op. 26], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Plaintive air, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 91/2)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, op. 30, B-flat major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 91/3)
        - Witches sabbath, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 91/4)
      - Goossens, Eugene
        - Don Juan de Mañara, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 91/5)
        - Two sketches for string quartet, Parts (Box-folder 92/1)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 2], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 92/2)
      - Gossec, François-Joseph
        - [Tambourin; arr.], Piano-violin score (Box-folder 92/3)
      - Graener, Paul
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 61], Piano-score and parts; List of prospective programs [?] written on verso of last page of cello part (Box-folder 92/4)
      - Grainger, Percy
        - Molly on the shore, String quartet parts (Box-folder 92/5)
        - Molly on the shore, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 92/6)
        - Irish tune from county Derry, Piano score (Box-folder 92/7)
      - Granados, Enrique
        - [Goyescas; arr.], Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 92/8)
        - Intermezzo, Piano score (Box-folder 92/9)
        - Intermezzo, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 92/10)
        - Spanish dance, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 92/11)
      - Grasse, Edwin
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op. 14, C major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 92/12)
        - Wellenspiel, Piano-violin score and part; Photostat of above (Box-folder 93/1)
      - Gretchaninov, Alexander
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 2, op. 2, G major], Parts (Box-folder 93/2)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 3, op. 75, C minor], Parts (Box-folder 93/3)
      - Grieg, Edvard
        - [Concerto, piano, op. 16, A minor; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 93/4)
        - Lonely wanderer, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Joseph Achron (Box-folder 93/5)
        - Grandmother's minuet, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Joseph Achron (Box-folder 93/6)
        - Puck (Kobold), Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Joseph Achron (Box-folder 93/7)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 27, G minor], Parts (Box-folder 93/8)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 27, G minor], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, F major], Parts (Box-folder 93/9)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 8, F major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 93/10)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 2, op. 13, G major], Piano-violin score and part; Second copy, piano-violin score only (Box-folder 94/1)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 3, op. 45, C minor], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 94/2)
        - Scherzo-Impromptu, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Joseph Achron (Box-folder 94/3)
        - Grieg album, Piano score (Box-folder 94/4)
        - Grieg album for pianoforte, Vol. II, Piano score (Box-folder 94/5)
        - Konzert Bearbeitungen für Violine und Klavier; arr., Arranger's holograph (Achron) piano-violin score (no. 5 of 7 wanting) (Box-folder 242/7)
        - Konzert Bearbeitungen für Violine und Klavier; arr., Photostat and negative photostat of arranger's holograph (Achron) piano-violin score (no. 5 of 7 wanting) (Box-folder 242/7)
      - Griffes, Charles
        - [Poem, flute, orchestra; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 94/6)
      - Grofé, Ferde
        - On the trail, Piano score (Box-folder 94/7)
      - Gruenberg, Louis
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 47], Holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 94/8)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 47], Photostat of holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 243/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 47], Photostat of holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 243/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 47], Parts (Box 95-96, Box-folder 97/1)
        - Four diversions for string quartet, Parts (Box-folder 97/2)
        - Four diversions for string quartet, Miniature score (Box 211)
      - Guastavino, Carlos
        - La rosa y el sauce (Box-folder 97/3)
      - Halffter, Ernesto
        - Sonatina/ballet en un acte, Orchestral score (Box-folder 97/4)
      - Halvorsen, Johan
        - Danses Norvegiennes, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 97/5)
      - Hammond, Richard
        - Notturno, scena e serenata, Photostat of holograph piano-violin score (2) (Box-folder 243/4)
      - Handel, George Frederic
        - [Concerti grossi, strings. Selections], Miniature scores (Box 211)
        - Larghetto, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 97/6)
        - [Sonatas, violin, continuo, op. 1], Piano-violin score and part; 2 volumes (Box-folder 98/1)
        - [Sonatas, violin, continuo, op. 1], Piano-violin score and part; Second copy, piano-violin score only (Box-folder 98/2)
        - [Sonata, violin, continuo, op. 1, E major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 98/3)
        - [Sonata, violin, continuo, A major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 98/4)
      - Haydn, Franz Joseph
        - [Duet, violin, cello], Parts (Box-folder 98/5)
        - [Quartets, strings], Violin I part; omits op. 77, no. 1-2, op. 103; First editon (1802) (Box 99)
        - [Quartets, strings], Violin II part (Box 100)
        - [Quartets, strings], Viola part (Box 101)
        - [Quartets, strings], Cello part (Box 102)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 2, no. 1, A major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 2, no. 2, E major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 2, no. 3, E-flat major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 2, no. 4, F major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 2, no. 5, D major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - 30 Berühmte Quartette [Band 1], Parts (Box-folder 103/1-2)
        - 30 Berühmte Quartette [Band 2], Parts (Box-folder 103/3, Box-folder 104/1)
        - Serenade, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 104/2)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 33, no. 2, E-flat major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 54, no. 1, G major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 54, no. 2, C major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 64, no. 5, D major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Vivace, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 104/3)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 76, no. 4, B-flat major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 76, no. 5, D major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Symphony, no. 85, B-flat major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Symphony, no. 88, G major], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 16, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 5, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 6, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 9, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 14, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 3, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 11, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 4, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 12, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 1, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Symphonie no. 2, Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Symphonies. Selections; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score; Folders: 104/4 Volume 1 104/5 Volume 2 (Box-folder 104/4-5)
        - [Trios, piano, strings], Piano score and parts; Folders: 105/1 Volume 1 105/2 Volume 2 105/3 Volume 3 (Box-folder 105/1-3)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, F-sharp major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 106/1)
        - [Trio, strings, op. 53], Parts (Box-folder 106/2)
      - Herbert, Victor
        - À la valse, Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 106/3)
        - [I'm falling in love with someone; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/4)
        - [A kiss in the Darkness; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/5)
        - [Thine alone; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/6)
      - Herold, Ferdinand
        - [Zampa. Overture; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 106/7)
      - Hindemith, Paul
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/8)
        - [Kammermusik, no. 4 (Violin-Konzert), op. 36, no. 3; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/9)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op. 11, no. 1, E-flat major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/10)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op. 11, no. 2, D major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/11)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, E major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/12)
        - [Trio, strings, no. 1, op. 34], Parts (Box-folder 106/13)
        - [Trio, strings, no. 2], Parts (Box-folder 106/14)
      - Honegger, Arthur
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 1], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/15)
      - Hoschna, Karl
        - Cuddle up a little closer lovey mine, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 106/16)
      - Hovhaness, Alan
        - Shatakh, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 106/17)
      - Howard, Joseph
        - Good mister postman, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 107/1)
      - Hřímalý, Jan
        - Tonleiter-Studien, Violin score; Laid in: Unidentified ms. (Box-folder 107/2)
      - Hubay, Jenö
        - Der Zephir, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 107/3)
        - [Scènes de la csarda, no. 3, op. 18; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 107/4)
        - [Walzer paraphrase, op. 105; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 107/5)
      - Ibert, Jacques
        - Bajo la mesa, Piano score (Box-folder 107/6)
        - [Quartet, strings], Parts (Box-folder 107/7)
      - Indy, Vincent d'
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 35], Parts (Box-folder 107/8)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 45], Parts (Box-folder 108/1)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, no. 2, op. 98, G major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 108/2)
      - Infante, Manuel
        - Gracia, 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 108/3)
      - Ireland, John
        - A holy boy, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 108/4)
        - [Phantasie, piano, violin, cello], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 108/5)
      - Jacob, Gordon
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 108/6)
      - Jacobi, Frederick
        - Con movimento dolce, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 108/7)
      - Jacobi, Victor
        - You are free, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 108/8)
      - Jenkins, Gordon
        - Homesick-that's all, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 108/9)
      - Jimenez, Marcos
        - Adios, Marquita Linda, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 108/10)
      - Joachim, Joseph See: Beethoven, Ludwig for cadenza to violin concerto (folder 29/6)
      - Juon, Paul
        - Árva, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 108/11)
        - [Berceuse, op. 28, no. 3], Piano score only; Violin part absent (Box-folder 108/12)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, op. 33], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 108/13)
      - Kabalevsky, Dmitri
        - [Colas Breugnon, op. 24], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [The comedians, op. 26], Orchestral score (Box-folder 109/1)
        - [The comedians, op. 26], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Improvisation, op. 21, no. 1], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 109/2)
      - Kálmán, Emmerich
        - [Countess Maritza, Play Gypsies-Dance Gypsies], Score (Box-folder 109/3)
      - Karłowicz, Mieczysław
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 8; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 109/4)
      - Kern, Jerome
        - All the things you are, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 109/5)
        - Make believe, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 109/6)
        - Ol' man river, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 109/7)
        - Smoke gets in your eyes, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 109/8)
      - Khachaturian, Aram
        - [Concerto, piano], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 109/9)
        - [Concerto-rhapsody, violin. orchestra; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 109/10)
        - Danse no. 1, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 109/11)
        - [Gayeneh. Selections], Miniature score; suite 1 (Box 211)
        - [Gayeneh. Selections], Miniature score; suite 1-A (Box 211)
        - [Gayeneh. Selections], Miniature score; suite 2 (Box 211)
        - Masquerade suite, Piano score (Box-folder 109/12)
      - Khachaturian, Karen
        - [Sonata, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 110/1)
      - Khrennikov, Tikhon
        - [Symphony, no. 1, op. 4], Miniature score (Box 211)
      - Knipper, Lev
        - [Symphony, no. 4, op. 41], Miniature score (Box 211)
      - Kodály, Zoltán
        - Adagio, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 110/2)
        - Duo, Parts (Box-folder 110/3)
        - [Háry János, op. 15; arr.], Piano score (Box-folder 110/4)
      - Korngold, Erich Wolfgang
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 35, D major], Photostats of ms. orchestral score (2) (Box-folder 110/5)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 35, D major], Parts (Box-folder 111/1-3)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 35, D major; arr.], Photostat of ms. piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 35, D major; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/1)
        - Vier Stücke, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/2)
      - Koutzen, Boris
        - Holiday mood, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/3)